http://www.silktrading.com/terms_privacy.asp

Go!
Custom Design Services
Legal Notices This website is provided by The Silk Trading Co., Inc. (The Silk Trading Co.) and may be used for informational purposes only. By using the site, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions set forth in these Legal Notices. If you do not agree to abide by these terms and conditions, then do not use the site. Any questions regarding these Legal Notices should be directed to: office@silktrading.comCopyright Copyright © 2012 LA Silk Trading Co., Inc. The images, text, organization and layout (collectively "Materials") of this site are copyrighted and protected by worldwide copyright laws and treaty provisions. Subject to fair use exceptions, the Silk Trading Co. does not authorize any downloading, distribution or republication of any Materials on this site. All rights reserved.   Trademark The Silk Trading Co.® is a registered trademark licensed by The Silk Trading Co., Inc., and may not be used without the express written consent of the owners of the registered trademark.   Privacy Statement Effective August 31, 2004Questions regarding this statement should be directed to office@silktrading.comThis website is the responsibility of The Silk Trading Co., Inc. The Silk Trading Co. can be contacted by e-mail: office@silktrading.com. The webserver on which this website is housed is maintained by The Silk Trading Co. The following policies apply to www.silktrading.com and all other websites owned and operated by The Silk Trading Co.   1. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors In order to access certain subscriber services or restricted areas within any of our web sites, we may require that you provide certain identifying information. This information may include your legal name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, subscriber name or screen name, password used to access our services, method of payment, and, if applicable, credit card number. We reserve the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain your account for use of these services. The Silk Trading Co. automatically collects and/or tracks (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of web browser of visitors to our web site, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with us via e-mail, post messages to our bulletin boards, or post messages to our chat groups, (3) information knowingly provided by the visitor in sales orders, registration forms, surveys, and contest entries, and (4) aggregate or specific information on what pages visitors access. Some Silk Trading Co. pages use a technology called "cookies" so that we can better serve visitors when they purchase a product on our web site, request additional information about our company, products or services, or participate in various activities posted on our site. These cookies may be used to obtain data such as the visitor's name, user-name, shopping cart, and pages or advertisements viewed by the visitor. When the visitor revisits the company's web site, we can recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor's experience accordingly. Although cookies are stored on the visitor's hard drive and not stored, in any form, by us, the visitor can set his or her browser to provide notice whenever a cookie is received, which gives the visitor the opportunity to decide whether to accept it or not. Certain Silk Trading Co. Web Site pages may have software installed within the page which provides us with information about the "clickstream" of our customers during their Silk Trading Co. Web Site visit. This software indicates which pages the visitors came from, what navigational paths they took, and which areas of the site they visited. Certain email communications you may receive from us, if you sign up for our email distribution service, may contain "Web beacons". Web beacons consist of a line of code on our site that delivers a small graphic image from another Web site or third party ad server. They may not be visible as the beacon is generally a 1x1 pixel that is often designed to blend into the background of a Web page. We use may use beacons to monitor the effectiveness of ad banners in our email distributions.   2. Use of Personal Data Collected Except for product purchases, personal data collected by us will only be used for marketing and promotional purposes, feedback purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development or enhancement, for content improvement, and to customize content and layout of our site, when requested by the Customer or Web Site User. Names, postal and e-mail addresses, and phone numbers collected may be added to our databases and used for future contact regarding new products and services, upcoming events, status of orders placed online, and customer service, only when requested by the Customer or Web Site User.   3. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties We maintain a secured area on our site for transmission of personal data, and store all personal data in a secure online database which is connected to the Internet or a private database which is not connected to the Internet or both. Although we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of the personal data you provide to us, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. We will have no liability for disclosure of such data due to errors in transmission or interception by unauthorized acts of third parties. It is the policy of The Silk Trading Co. not to share any information about our customers to third parties for except for the following purposes: we may disclose information to vendors who facilitate and/or support our customer transactions; we may disclose information to entities to whom we are legally required to disclose information; and/or we may disclose information to third parties where directed by a customer or with the customer's permission. Any third party with whom we have a relationship pursuant to which we provide or otherwise disclose data collected from visitors to our site will be carefully pre-screened, determined by us to be reputable, and will use the data provided solely for the purposes stated herein.   4. Opt-Out Rights Visitors may opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties (excluding any mandatory disclosure to government agencies and/or certain vendors who facilitate and/or support our customer transactions), or used by us to send promotional materials to the visitor, by contacting us by e-mail.   5. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data Upon request by e-mail or by mail, we will provide to visitors a summary of any personal information retained by us regarding the visitor. Visitors may modify, correct, or update their personal record or cause their personal record to be removed from our database. Company will only send personal records to the e-mail address on file for the visitor name associated with it.  6. Company's Right to Contact Visitors We reserve the right to contact site visitors regarding their account status and changes to any subscriber agreement, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.   7. Company's Right to Change Privacy Policy We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy.
